WILLIAM LEE

User Experience & Product Designer

415.786.0679 willcylee@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/willcylee wlee108.myportfolio.com

PROFILE

UI designer with a keen eye for detail and a deep focus on user needs. My background in quality assurance ensures that I create flawless and engaging digital experiences. Passionate about learning and always staying at the forefront of design trends.

SKILLS

Digital Media Design Graphic Design User Interface User Experience Photography Visual Design

TOOLS

Adobe CC Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop Adobe Lightroom Figma Notion Sketch

EDUCATION

San Jose State University, San Jose, MAY 2020

Major: B.S. Design Studies

Minor: Advertising

EXPERIENCE

Waymo via ICONMA & Cognizant - Software Quality Operations Associate

OCTOBER 2021 - OCTOBER 2023 | SAN FRANCISCO

- View and analyzed real world events to identify and escalate bugs in new self driving software, ensuring the safety and the quality of the Waymo autonomous vehicle
- Examined over 65+ events daily with a recall of 90% and escalation accuracy of 60%
- Triaged over 10000+ events using proprietary tools to find bugs in new software before release
- Performed simulations on new software to find logic errors and problematic maneuvers in the autonomous driving vehicle

ClassHook - UX/UI Intern

OCTOBER 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021 | SAN FRANCISCO

- Designed an intuitive playlist page prototype for users to save, share, and watch videos
- · Illustrated a mascot to promote the ClassHook brand
- Created a discussion question generator that provided users a way to search or create their own discussion questions for videos they watched, introducing new ways for teachers to engage students
- Conducted interviews with teachers and potential partners to obtain user feedback and to create a better overall user experience

Milagro Marketing - Visual Design Intern

JUNE 2018 - AUGUST 2018 | SAN JOSE

- Prepared a logo and designed apparel for El Teatro Campesino theatre company that helped revitalize the company
- Produced 10+ posters, flyers, signage and social media bugs that helped promote the annual Dia De Los Muertos event